

# Andrii Golub Middle frontend developer

Kyiv, Ukraine andrewgolub25@gmail.com https://t.me/flokiowl https://flokiowl.github.io/

## Summary of Qualifications

I am a dedicated self-taught frontend developer with 3 years of hands-on experience in Vue.js, HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. I take pride in developing responsive and user-friendly web applications and implementing UI/UX design principles to provide the best user experience possible. I am an effective team player with strong problem-solving and analytical skills.

#### **Skills**

HTML&CSS, JavaScript, VueJS, Git

#### **Experience**

## RegToEvent - Middle Frontend Developer

2020 - now

**Tech Stack:** HTML&CSS, SASS, JavaScript, VueJS, Git **Description:** I responsible for developing and maintaining three projects: an event management system, a course creation and employee training system, and a platform for creating landing pages and biolinks.

# **SOFTPRO - Junior Frontend Developer**

2019 - 2020

Tech Stack: HTML&CSS, LESS, JavaScript, Jquery, Handlebars,

SQL

**Description:** Development and support of online stores,

online pharmacies, open data geoportals.

#### **Education**

## **National University of Food Technologies**

2013 - 2017

Faculty: hotel, restaurant and tourism business

### Languages